ハンター協会の最高幹部 「十二支ん」を集結させた
Ah, this is the foundation I wanted!
ハンター「十二支ん」
I also want this lipstick and manicure spray.
会長が その実力を認めた１２人
Oh, what a cute wig...
有事の際に協会運営を託す他
Boss, we should get going soon. Just a little longer.
暇な時　遊び相手に なってもらったりしていた
I should buy this camisole too.
それぞれに コードネームが渡され
Her shopping's gonna be the death of me.
会長に心酔する メンバーのほとんどは
I concur.
会長！
Was there anything else we needed? Did you want anything, Eliza? No, nothing at all.
「十二支ん」 勢ぞろいかと思いきや ネズミがいねえな。
I have to go to the restroom.
副会長様は こんな時でも　お忙しいのよ。
It's okay... Watch my stuff for me.
こんな時だからでしょ？ 票固めに奔走してんのよ　きっと。
Will Kurapika be okay?
えん　会長！
I used my flute to help him recover a little.
ギンタ　うるさい！　暑い！　臭い！
How do you feel about the
whole assassins business?
ばっくれ屋のジンですら 来てるってのにな。 ネズミはクズだな。
The Ten Dons are hiring professionals
to handle the Troupe.
「ですら」って何だ　殺すぞ　サル。
Professionals? So, Kurapika...
お　やってみろボケカス。
I want you to join those hit men.
納得行かぬ！ なぜ　会長は　われらに お声を掛けてくれなんだ。 同感だ　モラウやノヴでは役不足！
Judging by his heartbeat, he wasn't entirely pleased
about joining the hit men. Of course not.
役不足の使い方　間違い。 自分で狩りたかったから… なのでは？
However, Kurapika is extremely determined.
ムッ…。
To achieve his goal, he's certainly
willing to sacrifice everything.
そろうまで待とう。
That's a hard road...
や　お待たせ！ ホントに申し訳ない！
I couldn't do it.
東ゴルトー関連で てんやわんやだよ。
What's the point of a life in which
you're basically killing yourself?
いや　参った参った　ハハハ…。
She's taking a long time.
いいから　早く座れ。 やっ　これは失敬。
Once we finish this job, I'm using the money to see
the world on my bike. That sounds really nice.
では早速
Not enjoying yourself is a crime.
次期会長選挙についての 議会を始めます。 ちょっと待て！　何で　おめぇが 当然みてぇに仕切ってんだ！
There are many ways to spend a life. Everyone has different ideas
about what's important.
あれ？　お気に召さない？
Huh?
遅れて来て 出しゃばってんじゃねえよ。
What's wrong? She's gone!
パリストン　うざい！ キモい！　消えろ！
Huh? What?!
いや　僕も　差し出がましいとは 思ったんだけどね。 何しろ　僕　ほら　副会長だし！
Daddy's such a liar! He wasn't going to take me to the auction!
みんなより少しだけ　役職　上だし そこそこ　まとめ役もできるし
Fine, I'll just go by myself!
実際の進行能力ならば チードルさん。
Come in.
どちらか　お願いできますか？
Forever Active
遠慮しとく どうせ　荒らされるもの。
One, two, three, four, five, six...
フフっ。
Looks like everyone's here.
同意。
No, not yet.
いいから　おめぇが司会　続けろ！
I thought the team only had eight members.
素直に 仕切りてぇって言えよ　クズが。
Nostrade is sending an additional person.
それでは　不肖　私　パリストンの 進行に異議のある方
Tsk, the guy who uses that
voodoo fortunetelling?
もちろん　不満が出たら その都度　審議にかけましょう。 僕は　いつでも引きますよ。
Then, has everyone arrived?
では　僕から提案です。 僕が会長に立候補しますから
The job is to annihilate the Phantom Troupe. When the auction kicks off again, they may show up.
選挙やめません？
If they do, dispose of them.
ぶち殺すぞ！　ガキが！
You're free to use any means you want. This team will be after the same target.
怖いなぁ　落ち着いてくださいよ。
We should decide how we address
each other when communicating.
だって　時間とお金の 無駄じゃありません？
Just use colors. Call me Blue.
結果は目に見えているのに。
I'll be Red.
ここにいる全員 誰も　あんたに入れやしないわよ。
It's like playing a game. Eh? What about you guys?
１１票。
Silva. I'm Zeno.
皆さん合わせて １１票ですよ　たかだかね。
Zeno? What color is that? We will both use our real names.
協会にハンターが何人いるか 知ってます？ ネテロ前会長は　強過ぎました。
What? You're welcome to call me by name, but I won't take orders. We'll do this our own way.
故に　弱者の気持ちが 分からないのです。
Silva and Zeno...
それは　皆さんも同じです。
Of the Zoldyck family?
僕なら弱者の痛みが分かる。
Let me know if you want someone killed.
そういう会長になります。 その弱者が　協専という名の 奴隷になってるよ。
I'm willing to give you a thirty percent
discount for being in the same line of work.
どのくらい 私腹を肥やしたのかしら？
They're from Killua's family.
ピンハネ王子様。 やだなぁ　誤解ですよ。
Does it really matter
あれは　プール金です。
what we call one another? Agreed.
協会をより大きくするための 積み立て制度ですよ。
There's no requirement we work together.
１８人… じゃあ　この数　何だか分かるか？
But we're talking about the Troupe. Attacking alone will be dangerous.
お前が副会長になって　３年間
Shaky teamwork will only cause confusion.
消息不明のハンターの数だ。
I will move alone. So it's 5 to 4.
命懸けだからこそ
We have our answer.
俺達プロは　信頼する者との 現状把握を怠らない。
The auction begins at nine.
We will transport you to the auction hall.
ハンターにとって消息不明は 変死より　よほど異常なこと。
Please wait here until it's time.
ちなみに　お前が就任する前は 年平均　０．６人。
Yo, Nostrade... How are you feeling? Not too bad.
今は１０倍だ。
Not too bad?
言うことは　あるか？ 不幸な数字だね　胸が痛むよ。
Not too long ago, you were just
leading a little country gang, and now you're acting like my equal.
僕が会長になれば きっと減ると思う。
I hear you've been rubbing your hands
together so much, your skin rubbed off. You okay?
立候補するよ。 ん？
It's sad when a man shows jealousy.
俺がジジイの遺志を継ぐ。
Bastard!
ジンさん 息子さん　大変らしいですね。 らしいな。 僕　お見舞いに行こうかな？
Let's be clear...
No one's impressed by you!
おう　喜ぶんじゃねえか？ えっ　アハハハハ！ 分かんないんじゃないかな？ 瀬死の重体だって聞きましたよ。
Many people envy my success, while they ignore their own failings.
やっぱり　やめときましょうか。
However, I intend to continue to rise.
行って死んでたら 無駄骨ですもんね。
By using Neon's fortunetelling.
行けよ　あいつは死なねえ。
I expect great things from you. You will be appropriately rewarded
when the time comes.
そもそも　まず立候補ってとこから 考え直しません？
The police are cooperating?
それは てめぇが言い出したんだろうが！
Sixty percent of the votes
どうなってんだ　てめぇの頭は！ あれは　経費と時間を
in the Yorknew City mayoral
election were bought.
削減できるならと思っての 発言で
And the police chief is the mayor's protégé.
手順を踏まざるを得ないなら やり方から決めましょうよ。
Redirecting traffic is quite easy for us.
こいつのペースに 巻き込まれると
Hello? Kurapika, it's terrible.
事が　どんどん ややこしくなりやがる
The boss ran away! She changed clothes in the restroom, so she must have planned ahead.
はぁ？　ふざけるな！
Then I can guess where she's going.
最高責任者を くじで決められっか！
Return to the hotel and stand by.
てめぇも　カスか？
What's wrong?
１２人に紙を配ります。
Your daughter's run away.
おい！
What?!
その紙に　全員投票　かつ 投票率９５％以上の
We probably have the same destination. The auction?
最善と思う投票方法を 書いてもらいます。
Damn, she's turned off her phone.
そして　第三者に　その中から 無作為に選んでもらう。
But Neon doesn't have a pass... She'll be turned away at the gate.
第三者…。 まっ　ビーンズでしょうね。
This is Light Nostrade! I need you to convey an order
to all the guards at the gate!
公平に１２分の１。 恨みっこなしなのでは？ うっ…　確かに。 悪くない。
If a girl about seventeen or
eighteen arrives with no pass, they should take her into custody! Her description...
いいですよ　僕　負けないですし。 ただ　誰の案か分かるように くじに名前は書きましょうね。
Okay, please go ahead. Whew, I was stuck without a way
to get past that gate.
１２分の１と言ってたが 違うな
Thank you so much. You're very welcome.
俺達１０人で　パリストン できればジンも
Really?! When was that?
…が　不利になる方法を 考えて書けば　６分の５
About five minutes ago... Her hair and attire were slightly
different, but it was probably her.
投票者が誰か 分かってしまう記名式では
She didn't have a pass?
パリストンが絶対有利
She didn't appear to realize that
the auction required a pass.
無記名で複数候補に ポイントを振り分ける方法なら どうかしら
She mentioned something about
her daddy, but then she left.
協専も　恐怖と罪悪感薄く 裏切れるのでは？
Yes, she got in a taxi alone.
この中に １２枚の紙が入っています。 １枚　引いてください。
Neon, where have you gone? I'll search for her.
それが会長選挙投票の ルールとなります。
Do you have a map of the city?
責任重大…　ですね。
I've heard that you're a good fortuneteller. Huh?
では　引きます。
What's your accuracy? They say I'm always right.
選ばれたのは
My hand moves on its own. Oh, how impressive.
ジンさんです。
Would you tell me mine? Sure.
グッ…　ジンのルール…
That's a strange name. My friends call me "boss."
こいつは パリストンとは違う意味で厄介
What? That's even stranger!
ルール　その１。
Then, I'll tell your fortune.
上位１６名で　再度　選挙を行い それでも決まらない場合
Your daughter is already in the
Cemetery Building on the auction site.
順次　人数を半分とする。
What? But how?!
ルール　その３。 投票率が９５％未満の場合 その選挙のみ　やり直すこと。
Regardless, we should hurry.
ルール　その４。
Okay, all done.
投票者は必ず 名前を記入すること。
May I have a look? Sure.
無記名は無効とする。
My fortunes are a little strange.
何　考えてんだ　てめぇは！ 何で記名式？
They usually have four or five verses.
あんたバカ？　完全なバカ？ おめぇらこそ　バカか？ あぁ？
Each one corresponds to
a week of the month, so the first may have already happened.
誰が誰に入れたか分かったほうが 面白いに決まってんだろ。
Oh...
こいつは　自分が楽しむことしか 考えねえ！
The calendar loses a precious component.
ルール　その５。 まだ　あったのか！
The remaining months gather to mourn.
選挙対策委員会　最高責任者は ジン＝フリークスとする。 そのてがあったか！
The mourners play a melody, while the eleventh moon quietly rises.
くじ引きで決めるのは 投票方法だったよね？ ルール４までは　ともかく
Amazing.
責任者は また別に決めることでしょ？ じゃ　４まででいいぜ。
It's correct. About this first verse... Huh? Oh, stop...
これが　ハンター…
I never look at the fortunes I write. Why not? I have a feeling they're more accurate
if I stay away from them.
恐ろしい…
Then may I ask you a question?
) )
This verse refers to a requiem for the dead.
) ((どうしたんですか？ こんなに早く))
Do you believe in the afterlife?
)
Hmm... Not really.
) )
My fortunes are for people who are alive.
)
Like you, Chrollo-san.
I'm guessing that the requiem
) )
is meant to help you, not the dead.
((会議室の電話の脇にでも 置いといてくれねえか？))
You're probably right.
((あぁ　同じものが 置いてありますよ))
Let's go.
)
They'll let us start browsing
at the auction soon.
) )
Actually, I heard that from someone else. Eh?
)
When I was little, I saw a
fortuneteller on TV say that.
) ) )
Really? So the fortuneteller tried to
avoid giving negative fortunes. Negative fortunes?
) )
The idea was to encourage people to wish for and
work toward better things.
) ((数日後には　「十二支ん」が 全員　ここに集まるだろう))
At the time, I was really moved...
) )
From then on, I wanted to be a fortuneteller.
死ぬほど長引く)) ((何しろ パリストンがいるからな))
The calendar loses a precious component.
((パリストンから見れば １２分の１でも
The remaining months gather to mourn.
自分に　より有利な方法になる 可能性があれば　上出来なんだ どっちにしろ　勝ち戦だからな))
The mourners play a melody, while the eleventh moon quietly rises.
６分の５になるって寸法だ)) )
The chrysanthemum withers and falls, to lie on the ground beside bloody Scarlet Eyes.
((言い出すのは… 本命　チードル))
But you will remain supreme.
)
Even after losing half your limbs.
Enjoy the interlude.
((くじを引くのが 私に…　なると？))
Search out new allies.
)
East is the direction to go.
((このビルの中 パリストン派の奴ばっかじゃん))
You will find one who awaits you.
((もし　そのルールで おめぇが納得するなら 三つ折りにして 当日まで持っててくれ)) )
A few years later, that fortuneteller
was arrested for being a con artist.
((もし　おめぇが 呼ばれなかったり
Are you talking about the Galactic Grandma?
呼ばれても 紙の折り方が違ってたら
Yep!
俺は　下を向いてるから その紙は燃やしてくれ))
I remember that she didn't
believe in the afterlife. Right, so that's why I don't, either.
((私は…　ジンさんが 会長を継いでくれるなら！)) ((あ　それは　ねえ ゼロだ　悪いな))
Personally, I believe in ghosts. Huh?
((結果を変えたくて やるわけじゃねえんだ))
And that's why I'll do as he
would have wanted.
((俺が継ぐのは ジジイの遺志だけだ))
What do you mean?
) )
Go wild.
((それを５番目に置いとけば 「ちょっと待て」って話になる))
Call a doctor!
((それで 俺がルール５を取り下げれば
We're on the first floor,
by the north elevator.
ルール４までが 通りやすいだろ？))
Someone's ill. Call an ambulance.
((チンピラと詐欺師の常とう手段さ 大した意味ねえよ))
We can't. They won't let an ambulance
inside without a pass.
((ルール５も通ったら 逆に降りる))
What did you say?
((ジンさん　結果が変わらないなら 何で　こんなことを？))
What if the unthinkable happens?! This is the daughter of the
Nostrade Family boss! Will you take responsibility for her life?!
((おめぇも おかしなこと聞くなぁ))
Tsk, got it.
((狙った通りに獲物が動けば ハンター冥利だろ？))
She has fans among the Ten Dons. Fine, we'll make it happen. Hey, call for an ambulance! Got it.
) )
Are you able to rewind this monitor?
選挙対策委員は 「十二支ん」全員の閣議制となり
That chop was incredibly fast...
投票用紙は　「十二支ん」の一人 クルックによって
Only I could have caught it. It's been a while since I was this excited.
全ハンターに届けられた
There is my prey.
第１３代会長総選挙
resting in room 501, on the fifth floor.
ハンター協会会員数６６１名 選挙立候補者　右に同じ
She shouldn't have been able to secure a pass...
投票用紙は　本人が持参し
How did she get in?
３名以上の 選挙対策委員が立ち会いの下
Your daughter's picture is on the Hunter website.
氏名の明記を確認した上で 投票箱に投函する 会場は ハンター協会本部ビル内
What? Most likely, someone found
this picture on the site, approached her, and then brought her here.
３名以上の選挙対策委員の 立ち会いがあれば
I'll find that person and kill him!
別地での不在者投票も可能
Please remain calm. I don't believe capturing your
daughter was their objective.
投票日時　本部時間 ８月８日　午前０時より
She may have been a hostage in case they
had trouble infiltrating the building.
８月８日 午後１１時５９分５９秒
It's dangerous here.
時間厳守　別地での投票も 本部時間に準じる
I called Melody and Basho. They should arrive soon. Can I trust them?
開票は即日とする
You should go with them. But the auction...
そして　８月８日　午前０時
This place will become a battlefield.
投票開始
The auction will be postponed again.
フッ　入れていいかな？
Addicted to murder.
殺人鬼は こんな世俗的なイベントには
Relax.
全く興味がねえと思ってたぜ。
I won't use any cheap tricks.
８５点
Let's play one-on-one.
うん　興味ないよ　ほら　白紙。
Yeah.
それじゃあ　何しに来た？ ９０点
I have a message from the boss. He wants to go wild in the Cemetery
Building, so we should come.
ジンって人いる？ いたら　話がしたくてね。
We aren't too far away.
あいつは　もう　いないよ。
What about everyone else? The rest had the same idea.
次に　ここへ来るのは 再選挙の時だとか。
They've been cleaning up the trash,
while approaching the building.
分かったら その紙切れ持って　帰れば。
Okay, then let's go.
７７点
Also, the boss actually added a rule this time.
あっそ。
A rule? What? Go absolutely crazy.
ぐぅ！ 品定め…　だな
The calendar loses a precious component. The remaining months gather to mourn.
１０点　２０点　４５点 １０点　２点　５０点 ３０点
The mourners play a melody, while the eleventh moon quietly rises.
プロのハンターといっても しょせん　こんなもんか やっぱり　次　戦うなら 「十二支ん」か
The chrysanthemum withers and falls, to lie on the ground beside bloody Scarlet Eyes.
あっ！ ９５点
But you will remain supreme.
え　第１３代会長総選挙の 投票結果です。
East is the direction to go. You will find one who awaits you.
過半数票　獲得者なし。
Why?
投票率８７．７％。
条件不達成により 再選挙が決定しました。
Why am I still alive?
おい！　見るくらい　いいだろ！
This is known as an Indoor Fish.
ダメです！ 単なる好奇心だって！
Made from Nen, it can only
exist in enclosed spaces.
誰にも投票用紙は 開示いたしません。
It's a carnivore that enjoys human flesh.
最高責任者に選ばれた以上 開票は全て私が一人でやります。
Its victims don't bleed or feel pain.
誰が誰に入れたか 見られなきゃ　意味ねえじゃん！ ケチ！　ハゲ！
And they won't die until the
Indoor Fish disappears.
アホ。
Won't die...
いろんなニュースがあったのさ。 それを　ちょっと並べ替えて ちょっと考えると
The calendar loses a precious component.
君が　アリか会長と 戦えたかもしれないのに。
The remaining months gather to mourn.
そのちょっとが面倒なんだよね。 イルミが僕の マネジャーしてくれないかな？ ゴンとキルアも アリ狩りに参加してね。
The mourners play a melody, while the eleventh moon quietly rises.
２人とも？
Uvo-san, can you hear us?
それだけは絶対に避けたい。
We are playing a requiem for you.
イルミ　ちゃんと説明しろ。 ゾルディック家には もう一人　弟がいる。
It was the start of a stormy night, fierce and drenched with blood,
yet somehow overwhelmingly sad.